So your first sexual experience was with a woman?
你的第一次是跟女人做？
I was 15. It was my best friend,Ruth.
我那年15岁 跟死党露丝在一起
And we got drunk on that hard cider.
西打太浓，我们醉了
And then suddenly, we were making out.
一不注意，我们已经在亲热了
Tell it again.
再说一次
Seriously.
我是褚的
Can that woman talk about anything else but sex?
那个女人就只会聊性爱吗？
Yeah,sure. Earlier she was talking about geography.
不会啊，她刚才在聊地理
She was listing the countries she's done it in.
她在列举她做过爱的国家
I think we all learned something.
大家都获益匪浅
Hey,you guys! Look what I found!
各位，看我找到什么
That's my mom's writing. Look.
那是我妈的笔迹，看
"Me and Frank and Phoebe, graduation,1965."
“我、法兰克与菲比 1965年毕业典礼”
-Do you know what that means? -That you're actually 50?
知道其中的含意吗？ 你已经50岁了？
That's not "me" Phoebe. That's her pal,Phoebe.
那个菲比不是我，是她的朋友
According to her yearbook, they were BFF.
毕业纪念册上说她们是BFF
Best Friends Forever.
永远的莫逆之交
That's great!
太棒了
I know! She probably has all kinds of stories about my parents.
我知道，她八成知道 我父母的事情
She might know where my dad is.
甚至知道我爸的下落
I looked her up. She lives by the beach.
我找过了，她住在海边
Maybe this weekend we can go there.
我们这个周末可以去海边
-Shoot,I can't go. I have to work. -That's too bad.
讨厌，我得工作 太可惜了
Big fat bummer.
真是扫兴
So tomorrow we'll drive out to Montauk.
那我们明天开车去莫陶克
Hey,Bonnie had sex there!
邦妮在那里做过
The One At the Beach
本集播出：“旧爱新欢”
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
Would you look at them?
你看他们
I'm never gonna find a boyfriend again.
我再也交不到男朋友了
I'm gonna die an old maid.
我会变成老姑婆
You're not gonna die an old maid.
你不会变成老姑婆
Maybe an old spinster cook.
可能会变成老厨娘
-Thanks. -Besides,worse comes to worse...
谢了 如果万不得已
... I'll be your boyfriend.
我会当你的男朋友
Yeah,right.
是啊
Why is that so funny?
有什么好笑的？
You made a joke,right?
你是在开玩笑吧？
So I laughed.
所以我笑了
A little too hard.
笑得太厉害了吧
Am I not boyfriend material?
我不适合当男朋友吗？
You're Chandler.
你是钱德
You know. Chandler!
你知道嘛，钱德
Okay,so we've established my name,and hit me.
我们确认了我的名字 还打了我一拳
But say we weren't friends. Say it's a blind date.
如果我们不认识 是别人介绍的
I show up at your door and I'm, like,"Hey,nice to meet you."
我来到你家门口，说 嗨，很高兴认识你
I'd probably be scared of a guy using a fake voice.
我会害怕压低声音的人
Oh,good. You bought food.
真好，你买了吃的
No,just my luggage.
不是，这是我的行李
I am having the best karma this week.
我这个星期的气很旺
I find this woman who knew my parents...
我找到认识我父母的人
...and then my client gives me his beach house.
客人又把海滩小屋借给我
What about that bike messenger you hit?
被你打的快递员呢？
Oh,I wasn't talking about his karma.
我不是在说他的气
Hey,check out the hat!
看看这顶帽子
Wait a minute,I know that hat.
慢着，我认得那顶帽子
I was taken aboard that hat.
我被戴上那顶帽子
They did experiments on me.
它们对我做实验
I can't have children!
我不能生育了
Seriously,where did you get the hat?
褚的，那是哪来的？
Ross gave it to me.
罗斯送的
I think she looks good.
我觉得她戴起来很好看
Did he buy it for you...
是他买给你的
...or win it for you?
还是抽奖抽到的？
Excuse me, my fashion-impaired friends...
很抱歉，这位时尚白痴
... I'm here to tell you hats are back.
帽子又流行回来了
And this time,they've ganged up and formed one giant super-hat.
这一回它们聚集成 一顶超级大帽子
Go,go,go!
快快快
Now everybody wants to be under the hat!
现在你们又想躲到帽子底下
What's with all this sand?
怎么这么多沙子？
Bob said there might be flood damage.
鲍伯说可能淹过水
Either that or he has a really big cat.
不然就是他的猫很大只
It's kind of an unusual house.
这个房子不太一样
It has three beautiful bedrooms and no baths.
有三个漂亮的卧房，没有浴室
But,you know,the ocean is right there.
但是大海就在旁边
IKnock,knock,knock.
有人在吗？
Hang on. Come in,come in.
请等一下…请进
Think about it and call me back.
你考虑完再打给我
Are you Phoebe Abbott?
你是菲比艾博特吗？
Surprise,Phoebe Abbott! I'm your best friend's daughter!
惊喜！我是你的死党的女儿
You're lrwin's daughter?
你是尔文的女儿？
I mean your old best friend. Here.
是以前的死党，你看
-Lily? From high school? Remember? -Oh,God,Lily. Yes.
高中的莉莉，记得吗？ 天哪，莉莉
Of course I remember Lily.
我当然记得莉莉
Then you must be
那你一定是…
Phoebe,Phoebe.
菲比
She named me after you,I guess.
应该是取自你的名字
Wow. Well. Look,there's Frank!
看，是法兰克
Yeah! Yes! Yes,yes!
对！没错！
That's my dad. That's Frank!
那是我爸爸法兰克
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy.
抱歉我这么激动
Take it easy. If you want,there's cookies.
别激动，那里有饼干
Or sangria! I could make sangria!
不然我调汽泡酒果汁
Sorry. Cookies are good,thanks.
不用，饼干就行了，谢谢
Anyway,I've been looking for my father.
总之，我一直在找我爸
-Have you heard from him or seen him? -Oh,no,I'm sorry.
你有他的消息或见过他吗？ 没有，对不起
I lost track of everybody after high school.
我毕了业就跟大家失去联络
Well,so tell me everything about my parents. Everything.
那就把我父母的事都告诉我
Oh,well,you know, we were always together.
你也知道，我们总是形影不离
-The other kids had a nickname for us. -What was it?
其他人帮我们取了个绰号 什么绰号？
The Three Losers.
俗辣三人行
Oh,poor Lily.
可怜的莉莉
I heard what happened. That must have been just terrible for you...
我听说她的事了 你一定非常难过
...Iosing your mother that way.
就这样失去母亲
Yeah,no,it was great.
不会啊，很棒
You know what a really good rainy-day game is?
知道下雨天玩什么最好？
I mean,naked game.
要脱衣服的喔
We should play strip poker.
我们应该来玩脱衣扑克牌
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗？
Come on. When you go away, you have to play. It's,like,a law.
拜托，出门一定要玩这个 这是一种规定
-All done. -Thank you.
好了 谢谢
Okay. Who's next?
下一个是谁？
No way!
不行
Come on,please. I'm bored. You let me do it once before.
拜托啦，我好无聊 你让我涂过一次
Well,if that's the rule this weekend....
如果这是本周末的规定…
-Get away. -Take it like a man. Come on!
走开 大方一点，来
Big bullies!
大坏人
How are we doing?
怎么样啊？
Bored and bored.
无聊到爆
You know what naked card game's never boring?
玩脱衣扑克牌最不无聊
So what's Phoebe like?
菲比是什么样的人？
I'm kind,caring and sweet. What's Monica like?
我心肠好又体帖，摩妮卡呢？
No,the other Phoebe. The one you went to see?
我是说你去找的那个菲比
I think she knows where my dad is!
我觉得她知道我爸的下落
Cool!
太好了
Where is he?
他在哪里？
She was pretending she hasn't heard from him...
她假装没有他的消息
...but I found this picture.
但是我发现这张照片
Isn't this what he would look like now?
他现在不就应该长这样？
Totally familiar.
很像
Why would she lie to you?
她为什么要骗你？
We're having dinner tomorrow. Maybe she'll tell me then.
我们明天要吃晚饭 也许她到时会告诉我
Maybe she just wanted to give him time...
也许她想给他一点时间…
...to buy me presents. I don't know.
帮我买礼物
So you're all bored?
你们都很无聊？
I'll close my eyes and point to someone. Whoever it is...
我闭上眼睛随便指 被指到的人
... has to think of something fun to do. And we have to do it.
要想一件好玩的事 大家就一定要做
Okay! Fan out! Fan out!
好，散开来
You know,we could just do this!
这样就很好玩了
We all have to play strip poker?
我们要玩脱衣牌
Strip Happy Days Game?
脱衣大富翁？
I couldn't find cards,so it was this or Strip Bag-Of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
我找不到扑克牌 不然就随便脱着玩
Done.
好
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up. Collect two cool points."
“走得漂亮，你得到两分”
Get five points,you get to make someone take off one item of clothing.
累积到五分 就可以叫别人脱一件衣服
It hasn't happened yet, but we're very excited.
还没人脱，但是我们很兴奋
Okay,come on.
来吧
Daddy needs a new electromagnetic microscope for Prehistoric Forensics.
我要替史前鉴识部 赢一台电子显微镜
"Take Pinky Tuscadero up to lnspiration Point.
“带粉红托斯卡罗到机会点”
Collect three cool points." Yeah!
“你得到三分”，漂亮！
Which gives me five.
我有五分了
And let's see,who is gonna lose their clothes?
我看看，谁要脱衣服啊？
I think I pick our strip poker sponsor,Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
我选本游戏的发起者 乔伊崔比亚尼先生
All right,relax. It's just a shoe.
放激动，只是一只鞋
"Your band is playing at Arnold's. Collect three cool points."
“你的乐队在音乐厅表演 你得到三分”
Which means I have five and that means I get Joey's boxers.
所以我有五分 乔伊要脱四角裤了
Fine. Gang up on me.
好，来对付我啊
I got you all, right where I want you.
我会让你们脱得很难看
Come on! Take them off!
快脱
Actually,it's kind of cold.
其实有点冷
What if I keep them on and give you a peek at the good stuff?
我能不能不要脱 让你们瞄一眼就好？
I'm gonna make more margaritas.
我再去调玛格丽特
What are you doing? Trying to get me drunk?
你干什么？想把我灌醉？
I'm just making margaritas.
我只是要调玛格丽特
Think I'll help her out.
我去帮忙
What is going on here?
这是怎么回事？
What?
什么？
You're painting his toenails. Chasing him around the room.
你涂他的脚指甲，追着他跑
Monica,please.
摩妮卡，拜托
He's totally flirting with you too.
他也跟你打情骂俏
He is,isn't he?
没错吧？
I don't know. Maybe it's just being here at the beach together...
不晓得，也许是因为来到海边
... but it's like something
感觉上…
Hi,Bonnie.
邦妮
My boss let me off early, so I took the train.
老板提早放人 我就搭火车来了
What are you guys doing?
你们在干什么？
We're playing Strip Happy Days Game.
玩脱衣大富翁
Cool! I'll catch up!
酷，我来赶进度
So you still don't think...
你还是不觉得我…
...I'm boyfriend material?
适合当男朋友？
I saw you checking me out during the game last night.
昨晚我发现你在打量我
You didn't even take off your pants.
你连裤子都没脱
Lucky for you.
算你走运
-What? -I don't know.
什么？ 我不晓得
Well,is everybody else having just the best time?
大家都开心吗？
Joey's asleep.
乔伊睡着了
He passed out. We put sand around him to keep him warm.
他昏睡过去 我们用沙子帮他保暖
Well,I assume the happy couple isn't up yet?
那对爱侣还没起床吧？
Did you guys hear them last night?
你们昨晚有听到吗？
I don't know what they were doing, but sea turtles came up to the house.
我不知道他们在干什么 但是海龟一度爬进屋里来
Good morning.
早安
-How'd you sleep? -Great.
睡得好吗？ 很好
Like a log.
跟木头一样
Us too.
我们也是
I'm going for a walk.
我要去散步
Good morning. Nice breasts by the way.
早安，好丰满的胸部
Hey,what happened to you?
你怎么没来？
Oh,nothing. I just felt like hanging out and reading.
没什么，我想在这里看书
The water was so great. We jumped off this pier and my suit came off.
海水好舒服，我们跳下桥墩 我的泳衣掉了
Sorry I missed that.
可惜我没看到
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
乔伊和钱德好好玩
I brought back half the beach in my hair.
我的头发里都是沙子
It was easier when I shaved my head.
以前光头方便多了
You know,I gotta tell you...
我一定要告诉你
...I just loved your look when you were bald.
我好喜欢你光头的样子
Really?
真的？
I think about shaving it again sometimes.
我有考虑重新剃光头
Really?
真的？
You definitely should do that.
你应该那样做
You know what? I should do it!
我是该那样做
You know what? Thank you. You are so cool.
谢谢你，你好酷
Oh,stop. Go on.
别这么说
-Now go shave that head. -All right.
去剃光头吧 好
What's the matter?
怎么了？
She canceled. My namesake canceled on me.
那个菲比取消了约会
She claims she had to go out of town. She's avoiding me.
她说她得进城去，她在躲我
She doesn't want to tell me where my father is. She knows!
她不想说出我爸的下落 她知道却不说
Pheebs,that sucks.
好差劲喔
Well,don't "Pheebs,that sucks" me yet.
先别跟我说差劲
-Where are you going? -She's out of town.
你要去哪里？ 她出门了
Something in her house will tell me where he is.
她家里一定有我爸的线索
Some people call that "breaking and entering."
有人称这种行为是闯空门
Well,are any of those people here?
这里有人这么想吗？
Look,I'll do something nice,okay?
我会做一些好事
I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
我会把制冰盒加水，好吗？
Hey,everybody!
你们看
Look what you did!
你看看你
You wanna touch it?
你想摸吗？
No,but it's great.
不想，但是很好看
Come on,touch it.
来嘛，摸嘛
You can feel all the bones in your skull.
可以摸得到头骨
I was having a little chat with Bonnie,and guess what?
我刚和邦妮聊了一下 你猜怎样？
She brought up who was behind the head-shaving idea.
她提到整件事的幕后主使
And now,who was it? Oh,that's right. It was you!
是谁呢？ 对了，就是你
That was her idea.
是她自己想剃
I just gave her a nudge.
我只是推了她一把
She said you gave her the razor.
她说你拿剃刀给她
So anyone up for a midnight dip?
有人要去夜泳吗？
-No,I'm good. -No,thanks.
我不要 不了
-Okay,I'll see you in a bit. -Okay,have fun.
待会见 好好玩
Come on,see? She doesn't look that bad.
也没那么糟嘛
You can see the moonlight bouncing off her head!
她的头可以反射月光
What were you thinking?
你在想什么？
I don't know.
我不知道
You balded my girlfriend!
你让我女朋友变成光头
All right.
好啦
Do you think it's easy for me to see you with somebody else?
看你跟别人在一起 难道我就好过？
You're the one who ended it!
是你要分手的
Because I was mad at you! Not because I stopped loving you!
因为我很气你 不是因为我不爱你了
You still love me?
你还爱我？
You still love me.
你还爱我
Yeah,so?
怎样？
You love me.
你也爱我
What does this mean?
什么意思？
I mean,do you want to get back together?
你想复合吗？
No! Maybe!
不是！也许吧
I don't know.
我不知道
I still can't forgive you for what you did.
我还是无法原谅你的行为
But sometimes when I'm with you, I just feel so....
但是有时和你在一起 我会觉得…
What?
怎样？
I just feel....
我会觉得…
-I just -What?
我… 怎样？
I feel
我觉得…
No! I don't care!
我不管
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker with you for practice!
我不要跟你练习一对一脱衣牌
But I made cards!
牌都做好了
Good night.
晚安
I'm going upstairs.
我要上楼去了
-Good night. -Good night.
晚安 晚安
Wanna play strip poker for practice?
要不要练习脱衣牌？
My ass!
我的屁股
Oh,it's me! It's me!
是我！
-I didn't wanna make any noise! -Then don't break in!
我不想发出声音 那就不要闯进来
-I'm sorry! -What are you doing here?
对不起 你来干什么？
I came to fill your ice cube tray.
我来帮制冰盒加水
What?
什么？
Okay,look.
好，是这样的
I took this picture from your fridge. I know that this is my father.
这是从你的冰箱上拿的 我认得这是我爸爸
This is Frank Buffay,and you were standing next to him!
这是法兰克布非 你站在他身边
I deserve to know where I came from.
我有权利知道我的身世
So if you can help me find my father, then you should.
要是你能帮我找到爸爸 你就应该帮我
Otherwise,you're just mean.
否则你就是坏人
So just tell me the truth.
把真相告诉我
All right.
好
The man in that picture is Chuck Mangione.
照片上的人是查克曼吉欧尼
My father is Chuck Mangione?
我爸是查克曼吉欧尼？
That's just Chuck Mangione.
他跟你没有关系
I sold him a house last year.
我去年卖给他一栋房子
And I'm very sorry,but I really don't know where your father is.
抱歉，我真的不晓得 你父亲的下落
And that's the truth.
这是实话
But you're right.
但是你说得对
I think a person should know where they come from.
人有权利知道自己的身世
Which is why l....
所以我…
I'm your mother.
我是你的母亲
I wanted to tell you yesterday,but I just...
我昨天就想说，但是我…
...felt all floopy,and....
我觉得很矬
You guys are getting back together.
你们肯定要复合了
She doesn't even know what she wants.
她自己都搞不清楚
Rachel's still mad at me.
瑞秋还在气那件事
Then you gotta back away. You don't need that kind of hurt.
那就打退堂鼓 你不需要受这种伤害
Take it from a guy who's...
听我的话，我…
... never had a long-term relationship.
从来没跟别人长期交往过
I know,but I really want to go up there and finish that kiss.
我知道，但我真的 很想上楼继续吻她
The water is great. You should go in.
水好舒服，你们应该去游泳
No,thanks. I just had an M&M.
谢了，我刚吃了M M
Well,good night.
晚安
Good night.
Don't be too long.
早点上来
Okey-dokey.
没问题
There is not one hair on that head.
真是清洁溜溜啊
It'll grow back,right? And she's really fun,and she's cool.
头发会长回来 而且她很风趣，很棒
And I'm finally moving on.
我终于往前走了
Getting over Rachel was so
要忘掉瑞秋实在…
I'm finally feeling sane. And if I go up there...
我终于恢复理智，要是我上楼
...and I kiss her....
吻了她…
God,I want to kiss her!
天哪，我好想吻她
And it doesn't work out. Do I wanna put myself through that again?
要是失败呢？ 我真的想再心碎一次吗？
Let me get this straight.
我想问一下
If you go with Bonnie,you do the smart,healthy thing and move on.
选择邦妮是明智的决定 可以抛开过去
Right? And if you go with Rachel, Bonnie's free tonight?
对吧？要是选择瑞秋 邦妮今晚就空下来了？
Hi there.
你好
That's that weird voice again.
你的声音又怪怪的了
Let me try it again.
再试一次
You'll wanna date this next guy, I swear!
下一个人你一定喜欢
Hi,I'm Dorf!
你好，我是小矮人
Your date for the evening.
你今晚的男伴
Oh,come on. Dorf on dating? That's good stuff!
小矮人约会耶 多有意思啊